Guide to the Administrative Research Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Administrative Research Office, Yale University, records
1974-1978
RU 716
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(1 box)
The records consist of budgets, statements and committee material documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Administrative Research Office.
Yale University. Administrative Research Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-F (YRG 5-F), Records documenting operations and administrative services at Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of budgets, statements and committee material documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Administrative Research Office.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by alphabetically by subject.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Administrative Research Office
- Records, 1974-1978; Accession 1978-A-012
  - Administrative Research Office
    - ARO Budget Maintenance Sheets, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ARP List of Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ARO Projects Status Reports (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Research Personnel
    - General (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Marvin Curtis (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Christopher Grannis (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Kathleen Mate (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Center Projects
    - General (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Humanities (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Physical Sciences (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Social Sciences (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AREA (Management Issues Forum) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Casual Payroll Project
    - Casual Payment Form and System - 1978 Ad Hoc Committee (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Forms and Procedures (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Overtime Compensation Study (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Copier Project
    - Copy Center Utilization Study (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Historical Cost Studies (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - YQCC and MSCC Billing Study (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Financial Transactions
    - ARO Financial Statements, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - ARO Service Requests, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - ARO Monthly Statements, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - ARO Service Requests, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - ARO Monthly Statements, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Forms Control Project
    - Committee on Forms Usage (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Consolidated Transfer Form (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Consulting Agreement Form (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Forms Control Project (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Request for Check Form (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Salary Verification Form (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Scholarship/Fellowship Forms (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - General Incoming (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Mail Processing Project
    - Mailing Lists (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Mail Processing Project (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous ARO Projects (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Personnel Systems
    - Personnel Forms and Procedures (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Personnel Profile Form (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell Review (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Telephone Message Center Project (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - United Way Campaign, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Office Equipment and Furniture Inventory (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Appeared on statement: our copy of stock requests, purchase requests, requests for service, casual forms (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Received: our copies of stock requests, purchase requests… (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Computer services correspondence (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Telephone services correspondence (Box 1, Folder 44)